The human side of the digital revolution.
Lo and Behold: Reveries of the Connected World is a
documentary film directed by Werner Herzog.
Werner Herzog's exploration of the Internet and the connected world.
Self, played by Elon Musk.
Self, played by Lawrence Krauss.
Self, played by Werner Herzog.
Self, played by Lucianne Walkowicz.
Self, played by Leonard Kleinrock.
Self, played by Ted Nelson.
Lo and Behold, Reveries of the Connected World is a 2016
American documentary film directed by Werner Herzog.
In it, Herzog ponders the existential impact of such things as the Internet, robotics,
artificial intelligence, and the Internet of things on modern human life.
The leaders in the field of technology who are interviewed in the film include
Leonard Kleinrock, Bob Kahn, Ted Nelson, Sebastian Thrun, and Elon Musk.
The film, which was sponsored by the company NetScout,
premiered at the 2016 Sundance Film Festival.
The film explores themes of artificial intelligence (a.i.),
planet mars, hacker, solar flare, space.